Galarc Kingdom, Duke Cretia's territory, Nor
So, that's...
It could indeed look like a dragon to some.
Fortunately, it doesn't
seem to have noticed us,
but I decided that continuing our
flight to Amande was dangerous,
and made an emergency landing.
It was a quick and fitting decision, Captain.
You have my heartfelt gratitude.
Thank you. I am extremely
grateful to hear you say that.
Lady Liselotte,
that appears to be the enchanted
airship of Duke Huguenot's family.
Spirit Chronicles 2
All of you, lower your barriers and
commence attacking individually.
Magic Cannon!
Heroes and Champions
Lady Liselotte.
Welcome. It has been some
time since last we met.
It has indeed, Baronet Bochsa.
Hey, Liselotte!
Did you meet Beltrum's Hero?
Sir Hiroaki!
Yes, thankfully. I was able to safely
deliver an invitation to their Hero as well.
But whyever are all of you here?
Huguenot said he had business in Galarc.
He said he'd be stopping in
Amande, so I tagged along. But...
You encountered that while in flight.
That's about the size of it.
It seems necessary to meet
immediately to share information
and discuss what measures to take.
Baronet Bochsa, might I ask
you to provide a space for us?
Of course. I'm afraid it isn't very large,
but you're welcome to come to my mansion.
Beltrum Kingdom, Capital of Marquess Rodan's territory, Rodania
Marquess Rodan's lands are impressive.
Even though their lord has been
banished from the royal capital,
this place is very lively.
Yes, you're right. Oh.
Where is Aishia?
What?
Aishia!
What are you doing?
Are you this lovely lady's attendants?
Y-Yes, I'm sorry.
Um, how much do we owe you?
Oh, don't worry about that.
It's that man's treat.
Do you two want something
to eat, too? It's good!
Oh, no. We couldn't.
No need to hold back!
He worked to ready the ship for the Hero.
Apparently he got paid
a heap of money for it.
He said he wanted to share his luck.
He prepared a ship for the Hero?
That's right!
And he said something about the
Heroes who were summoned here
being invited to some kind
of presentation party.
What kind of people are the Heroes?
Do you know their names?
Sorry. I don't know.
Then where is the Hero's
ship setting sail for?
Oh. They set out today with the
princess and her people for Galarc.
So, basically, it's bad that
dragon-type thing is around?
Yes. It's certainly not something
we humans are prepared to deal with.
In the worst case, we would have to consider
abandoning the town and
evacuating the citizens.
When it comes to the citizens of Nor,
you may entrust them to me.
Of course. Thank you.
Duke Huguenot, what do you think?
Indeed. What to do?
Can I say something, Liselotte?
What are you guys planning to do?
I plan to return to Amande.
I've left a representative in my place,
but I am the governor of that city.
Hang on. You're planning to
use an enchanted airship?
If you fly in one of those, you'll
antagonize that thing, right?
Yes, which is why I plan to return by land.
Fortunately, if we leave tomorrow morning,
we should arrive while it's still light.
Over land? Just you and your lady's maids?
There is no need for concern. My attendants
have all been trained for combat.
Sir Hiroaki, you mustn't inquire too
deeply into someone else's business.
You'll bother Lady Liselotte.
Roanna. But still...
No. I get it. Yes, I understand very well.
You understand?
I'll go with you, Liselotte.
What?
Sir Hiroaki!
I'm a Hero. I can't just stand
idly by in this situation, can I?
Still...
Now, wait, Roanna.
We cannot simply ignore Sir Hiroaki's wishes.
B-But, Duke Huguenot...
Sir Hiroaki is a Hero.
We are in no position to
give orders to him.
That is...
Wait, please, Duke Huguenot.
Sir Hiroaki is a Hero from
a country other than my own.
I can't possibly expose him
to danger for our sakes.
Liselotte, just listen.
I am acting as a Hero here. I swore that
I would help Duke Huguenot and his allies,
but that's only under the condition
that I'm convinced it is necessary.
Running off to somewhere safe on my own...
That violates my personal
sense of aesthetics.
As that is the situation, what do you think?
Even if the unforeseen should happen,
we swear that we shall not press
you to take responsibility.
Are you in earnest?
I am.
It would be more trouble if Sir Hiroaki
were to act completely independently.
Is this satisfactory, Princess Flora?
Y-Yes.
After all, we couldn't possibly take shelter
and leave Sir Hiroaki here on his own.
And I'm only escorting
them from here to Amande.
It can't be that dangerous, right?
And if the situation goes bad, that's
when you should count on me the most.
That's...
The sign of a Hero...
my Divine Arms, Yamata no Orochi!
Yamata no... Orochi?
That's right. I'm the one who named it.
Understood.
Aria!
Might you be Aria Governess?
Do you know him?
Pardon my rudeness.
I have been entrusted with your safety today.
I am a knight captain under Duke Huguenot's
command. My name is Raymond Brant.
I am very pleased to meet
you, Lady Liselotte.
Yes. Thank you for looking
after us, Sir Raymond.
And are you an acquaintance of Aria?
It has been quite some time,
Sir Raymond Brant.
Then you really are Aria!
I've been wondering about you all this time.
What happened to your family was...
Well, it was very unfortunate.
For you to think of me, someone from a
ruined family, at all... I'm most grateful.
At the moment, fortunately, Lady Liselotte
has taken me in, so I am doing well.
Liselotte!
It seems the Hero has arrived.
Will you be ready to leave shortly?
Duke Huguenot, good morning.
Rattling around in a carriage every
once in a while isn't bad at all.
You mustn't let down your guard, Sir Hiroaki.
Don't worry so much.
Princess Flora,
I realize you aren't accustomed to
riding in a carriage over rough roads.
If you feel uncomfortable,
please don't hesitate to tell me.
Oh, no, it isn't that.
I'm just not very good with words.
Listening to others speak like
this is more relaxing for me.
Please pardon my discourtesy.
If you'd like, will you speak with me?
With all due respect, there is so much
I'd like to know about you, Princess Flora.
Yes, I would love to!
Hey, don't forget about us!
Of course. Would you—
Stop the carriage!
There are monsters in the area!
Everyone, battle formations!
Wh-What's going on?
What is it? Monsters?
Where are they?
An incalculable number of monsters lies
hidden in the forest on either side of us!
Spirit Chronicles 2
This isn't right. The monsters'
presences appeared so suddenly.
How?
Knights, hurry! Your shields!
What is this? What's going on?
Magic Barrier!
If you're wounded, stay near the carriage!
Duke Huguenot, please don't come outside!
Captain Raymond! Please leave
the forward defense to me!
Understood!
There are monsters on the road to the rear!
There are monsters ahead.
It can't be. A hundred.
Two hundred. Three hundred?
How many of them are there?
They're coming from the woods on either side!
Lady Liselotte, please stay low in
the carriage and don't come out.
The walls of the carriage should be
able to withstand some thrown rocks.
I will.
I will eliminate the enemies ahead of us.
After I have commenced my attack,
all of you, lower your barriers and
commence attacking individually.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Knights, please continue your defense.
Leave the attacking to us.
Magic Cannon!
That's the Headhunting Princess
for you. She's so dependable.
Don't just stand and watch.
We have to begin our attacks, too.
All right.
Now, Grace!
Natalie, Chloe, and I will
figure out what to do here.
You four, handle the other side, please.
Understood.
Let's go.
Enchant Physical Ability.
Chloe, stay behind the knights and use
Photo Bullet to defeat the weaker monsters.
Be careful not to hit our allies.
Yes, ma'am.
Now, let's go, Natalie.
Understood. I'm ready any time.
Enchant Physical Ability.
There is one incredible woman here.
She must be Liselotte Cretia's
weapon and right hand.
The defense on either side is quite strong.
Liselotte's underlings are truly skilled.
Still, there are weaknesses to exploit.
Hey!
What's going on out there?
Everything's fine, right?
Everything is fine.
Everyone out there is a professional
when it comes to battle.
Still... there are all those knights,
and this still isn't done?
What's going on?
Sir Hiroaki, let's trust in everyone.
What? Those guys out there
haven't explained anything.
I can't trust a bunch of
people I don't really know.
I'd be a fool to trust them, right?
But...
I'm terribly sorry.
I'm embarrassed to admit it, but I'm scared.
Would it be all right if I held
hands with you, Princess Flora?
Yes!
Oh, Roanna! You must be scared!
If necessary, I'll unleash the power of
Yamata no Orochi and protect you.
Don't worry.
How very reassuring.
Wh-What was that?
What fell on us?
There isn't a monster up there, right?
I don't know!
I've hit my limit!
We're going out there!
S-Sir Hiroaki!
Wait, please!
Sir Hero?
Honestly! He takes such looking after!
U-Um, what should we do?
We need to go after Sir Hiroaki.
I'll check the situation outside. Please
make sure not to get separated from me.
All right.
Magic Barrier.
What is that?
Were all of these monsters
hiding in the woods?
Princess Flora, this way.
All right.
H-Hey! So, you came out, too?
Are you all right?
All right? Of course not!
What's going on here?
Can we win?
That isn't for us amateurs to decide.
But it seems that, at the moment,
their teamwork is holding.
Let's hope that they can
make it through this.
Oh, come on! What's with this crappy world?
The Hero with the cheat skills
is supposed to be super useful
in their first battle, right?
No one wants things to be
on hard mode like this!
Lady Roanna.
Can I ask you to look after Princess Flora?
I'm going to go use my
magic to treat the wounded.
Of course. I will leave the rest to you.
Very well.
Lady Liselotte!
Hey, wait. Liselotte!
What is this? It's like one of those stressful
turns of events that always happens!
Are you conscious?
Heal.
My lady, are you all right?
Yes, but more importantly,
what's the situation right now?
We're being pressed into defense
on either side and the rear.
I've taken care of most of
the monsters to the front.
I'm leaving the remainder
to the other attendants
and I'm on my way to support the rear.
I see. Then, take care
of it quickly, won't you?
I'm depending on you.
Understood. I will be back soon.
All right. Now, I have to do
the things that I can do, too.
So, she's gone to the rear.
It seems the diversion was a success.
Now, then...
She's terrifying.
Is it the power of that enchanted blade?
No, the power is hers.
That's...
I believe I will suffice to take
care of the monsters in this area.
Can I ask you to go and support
the flanks and the front?
R-Really? You're incredible.
What's that?
This can't be real.
I-Is that the one from back then?
Lady Roanna, have you
seen that monster before?
I-It's a minotaur!
It's a legendary monster that
raged during the Divine-Demon War!
Oh, come on. That's the end for us, right?
Where did that come from?
Lady Liselotte!
Princess Flora!
I'll help.
It's just like back then.
Lady Liselotte!
Who are you?
We can talk later.
An enchanted sword?
That can't be real! He knocked
that giant monster away?
Hooray! He did it!
Next Time
Lynchpin of Memories
"Lynchpin of Memories."
Spirit Chronicles 2
ROAR
Illustration: Minazuki Futago